GAUTAM NALAWADE

Unity Developer

📞 +91 9870564513 💮 gautam.v.nalawade@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Unity/C# - Software Development Engineer

03/2022 - 09/2023

Jio Tesseract Imaging Pvt. Ltd.

Navi Mumbai, IN

- Worked on 3 AR/VR projects that run on Jio Glass and Jio Dive with the help of Tesseract Mixed Reality SDK.
- Gained experience of working in collaboration with UI/UX designers, Android/iOS developers, Web developers and QA's to meet end product requirements.
- Integrated 3rd party plugins namely Vuplex Webview, AVPro and ClearVR in Unity projects.
- Learned to use project management tools namely JIRA, Bitbucket, Sourcetree, Git and Confluence.

Unity/C# - Software Developer

06/2020 - 03/2022

IDZ Digital Pvt. Ltd.

Navi Mumbai, IN

- Worked on 5 live games and developed around 20 prototypes in 2d and 3d across categories like word games, puzzle games and board games in Unity.
- Learned and built 2D and 3D games using Unity engine and C# programming.
- · Worked on bug fixing and feature development of published games.
- · Worked on building quick prototypes in Unity for demonstrating game ideas.
- Integrated localization with more than 10 languages using Unity Localization Package.
- · Worked on online multiplayer using Photon plugin for a 2d board game.

Application Support Engineer

01/2019 - 05/2020

Wipro Limited / ThinkApps Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

Navi Mumbai, IN

- Voice/Mail/Chat Support for Client In-house POS applications.
- Guiding the correct usage of applications and providing troubleshooting for technical issues.
- Staying updated about the changing functionality of the applications. And also the new issues and troubleshooting that follows.

Business Development Executive

02/2018 - 10/2018

SpryOX Pvt. Ltd.

Navi Mumbai, IN

- Involved in lead conversion, requirement gathering and client management.
- Platforms used for generating business: Justdial, Freelancer, Fiverr, Upwork, Facebook

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Technology

06/2014 - 06/2017

Mumbai University

Navi Mumbai, India

GPA 7.25 / 10

Diploma in Computer Technology

06/2011 - 06/2014

MSBTE

Mumbai, India

Percentage | **67.3** / 100

SUMMARY

With 3 years of combined experience in mobile game development and AR/VR application development, I am always striving to learn and explore more in software development as a whole. My career objective is to grow in the world of software, putting best possible efforts and trying hard that every effort invested is worth mentioning in the long run. I am having experience of working in small as well as large teams, and on-site as well as remote.

SKILLS

Unity Game Engine C# · JIRA ·

Confluence · Git · Bitbucket ·

Sourcetree · Game Development

PROJECT LINKS

Jio Tesseract Projects

Jio Immerse VR application

IDZ projects
Snake and Ladder

Family Board Games

1 Word 2 Pic Word Puzzle Game